<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mastering PostgreSQL</title>
    <link>http://masteringpostgresql.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Mastering PostgreSQL</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2017, Dimitri Fontaine</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:08:35 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://masteringpostgresql.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About the Author</title>
      <link>http://masteringpostgresql.com/post/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://masteringpostgresql.com/post/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi! My name is Dimitri Fontaine and I have been using and contributing to Open Source Software for the best of the last twenty years. I took role as developer, maintainer, packager, release manager, software architect, database architect and administrator, sometimes devops. In the same time frame, I also have started several companies (they are still thriving) with a strong Open Source business model, and I have been in manager positions at times too, including at the Executive level in big companies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering PostgreSQL in Application Development</title>
      <link>http://masteringpostgresql.com/about/book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://masteringpostgresql.com/about/book/</guid>
      <description>I am writing a book to share my knowledge about how to best use PostgreSQL as an application developer. If you&amp;rsquo;ve ever asked yourself how much should I have my database do for me? this book is for you. If you&amp;rsquo;re thinking that using an ORM might not always be the best option out there, if sometimes you wish SQL was easier to maintain than those concatenated strings with conditionals, then this book can&amp;rsquo;t wait for you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frequently Asked Questions</title>
      <link>http://masteringpostgresql.com/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://masteringpostgresql.com/faq/</guid>
      <description>All you wanted to know about Mastering PostgreSQL in Application Developement, the book you need to read as a developer to level-up your SQL game!
 The book isn&amp;rsquo;t what I expected it would be, at all. Mastering PostgreSQL in Application Development is a book that teaches SQL to application developers. If it&amp;rsquo;s not of any value to you, then just say so and I&amp;rsquo;ll refund you, no question asked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering PostgreSQL Services</title>
      <link>http://masteringpostgresql.com/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://masteringpostgresql.com/services/</guid>
      <description>Coming Soon! SQL Training. SQL Coaching. SQL Consulting. PostgreSQL!
It&amp;rsquo;s coming soon. Any question? Email Us.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>